[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It was one of the first TV shows for children.  It featured one human and many puppets, all worked by one man, Burr Tillstrom.  What was its name ?", "correct_answer": "Kukla, Fran and Ollie", "incorrect_answers": ["Howdy Doody", "Crusader Rabbit and Rags the Tiger", "Wonder-Rama"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year was the romantic comedy movie Sweet Home Alabama released in theaters?", "correct_answer": "2002", "incorrect_answers": ["1999", "2004", "2000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the approximate surface of the skin of an average adult human?", "correct_answer": "From 1.5 to 2.0 square meters", "incorrect_answers": ["Between 0.5 and 1.0 square meters", "From 2.0 to 2.5 square meters", "Between 3.0 and 3.5 square meters"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is an efficient way to save trees?", "correct_answer": "Using less electricity", "incorrect_answers": ["Using the washing machine", "Using less water", "Killing animals instead"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which astronomical phenomenon is also a popular programming environment?", "correct_answer": "Eclipse", "incorrect_answers": ["Polar lights", "Equinox", "Comet"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which country was the term television coined?", "correct_answer": "France", "incorrect_answers": ["Canada", "The USA", "The United Kingdom"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This crab is not really a crab, but an arthropod. Its closest relative is the spider.", "correct_answer": "Horseshoe crab", "incorrect_answers": ["Fiddler Crab", "Spider Crab", "Rock Crab"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which part of the world was coffee first prepared as a beverage?", "correct_answer": "Ethiopia", "incorrect_answers": ["China", "Peru", "Colombia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the capital of Afghanistan?", "correct_answer": "Kabul", "incorrect_answers": ["Tirana", "Dushanbe", "Tashkent"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Before he started making movies in Hollywood, Dudley Moore was part of a comedy duo in Great Britain in the late 60 and early 70s. What was his partners name?", "correct_answer": "Peter Cook", "incorrect_answers": ["Peter Baker", "Less Parks", "Jim Jackson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to the movie Smokey and the Bandit, in CB radio speak, a 10-100 means you have to use the bathroom.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who wrote and illustrated the famous childrens book The Tale of Peter Rabbit, first published in 1902?", "correct_answer": "Beatrix Potter", "incorrect_answers": ["Hans Christian Andersen", "Oscar Wilde", "Lewis Carroll"]}]